{
    "question": "B, ESSAY    1.\r\nEnergetic\r\nFunny\r\nShy\r\nSelfish\r\nFill in the gaps. Use the words in the box !\r\na My uncle loves to tell Jokes to make us laugh. He is.\r\nb. She never talks to a stranger. She is very\r\nc I like doing sports and physical activities. I'm very\r\nd Don't just think of yourself, that's so\r\n2. Read the text below and answer the questions!\r\nMy name is Dinl. I use the web only on weekends. I\r\nvisit a lot of websites. My favorites websites are\r\ngame websites and science websites. I'd like to\r\nknow about all the latest Inventions. I like science\r\nvery much. Someday, I want to be a scientist.\r\na. What does Dini want to be?\r\nb. What kind of websites does she like?\r\nc When does she visit the websites ?\r\nd Why does she visit the science website ?\r\n3. What is the object?\r\na. It is for writing letters on the white board. It is\r\nb. They are for cutting things. It is\r\nC. It is for sharpening your pencil. It is\r\nd. It is for sweeping the floor. It is\r\nI'm proud of my school. Our teachers are smart. We have\r\nmany good books and magazines in our school library. The\r\nclassrooms are not big, and they are clean and tidy. But, the\r\nschool yard is very small. There are not many plants, so it is\r\nvery hot in the afternoon.\r\nWhat Siti likes and does not like about her school:\r\nThings she likes\r\nThings she does not\r\n(like\r\n1.\r\n2.\r\n2.\r\n5. Fill in the blanks with has or have.\r\na. They\r\nb. She\r\nC. Does Bobby\r\nd. Rabbits\r\nfluty fur.\r\na big dog.\r\na fish?\r\nlong ears\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. a) funny</p><p>b) shy</p><p>c) energetic</p><p>d) selfish</p><p>2. a) a scientist</p><p>b) game websites and science websites</p><p>c) only on weekends</p><p>d) because she like science and she want to be a scientist someday</p><p>3. a) marker</p><p>b) scissors / knife</p><p>c) sharpener</p><p>d) broom</p><p>4. things siti likes:</p><ul><li>the teachers are smart</li><li>there are many good books and magazines in siti&#039;s school library</li><li>the classrooms are clean and tidy</li></ul><p>things siti doesn&#039;t like: </p><ul><li>the school yard is very small</li><li>there are not many plants, so it is very hot in the afternoon.</li></ul><p>5. a. they have....</p><p>b. she has....</p><p>c. does Bobby has....</p><p>d. rabbits have....</p><p>e. a big dog has....</p><p>f. a fish has....</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu, maap kalo salah\u270c</p>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1)</p><p>a. funny</p><p>b. shy</p><p>c. energetic</p><p>d. selfish</p><p>2)</p><p>a. Dini wants to be a scientist</p><p>b. She likes game websites and science websites</p><p>c. She visited the websites only on weekends</p><p>d. Because she&#039;d like to know about all the latest inventions</p><p>3)</p><p>a. \u00a0a boardmarker</p><p>b. knives</p><p>c. a sharpener</p><p>d. a broom</p><p>4) She likes smart teachers and clean and tidy classroom.</p><p>She doesn&#039;t like small classroom, yard that is not green, and hot temperature.</p><p>5(</p><p>a. have</p><p>b. has</p><p>c. has</p><p>d. have</p><p>6) (Fluty???? is a sound of a flute or fluffy fur : covered with fur)</p><p> </p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "27-desi-do-you-mind-if-i-use-your-pen-to-sign-this-paper-jus-353",
            "question": "27. Desi    \"Do you mind if I use your pen to sign\r\nthis paper?\"\r\n\"Just a moment. I haven't finished\r\nwriting my curriculum vitae.\"\r\nArif\r\nWhat does the woman want?\r\nA To borrow a pen.\r\nB. To buy some paper,\r\nC. To write an article.\r\nD. To ask his paper,\r\nE. To finish her writing\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>A</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Artinya</p><p>Apakah kamu tidak keberatan kalau aku pinjam pulpen kamu buat tandatangani kertas ini?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>A.To borrow a pen </p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>Desi ingin meminjam pena milik arif tapi,</p><p>Arif sedang menggunakan penanya untuk menyelesaikan tugasnya.</p><p></p><p>See you at the next answer </p><p>Pawuuu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "who-is-the-father-of-indonesian-education-300",
            "question": "Who is the father of Indonesian education\r\n\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Ki Hajar Dewantara </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Hope its can help you^^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Ki Hadjar Dewantara</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>Adalah sosok yang dikenal sebagai bapak pendidikan nasional </p><p></p><p>Hari dimana diperingati hari pendidikan nasional 2 Mei ini diambil dari tanggal kelahirannya.</p><p></p><p>See you at the next answer </p><p>Pawuuu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-incomplete-text-is-for-36-to-38-the-most-destructive-landsli-708",
            "question": "This incomplete text is for 36 to 38    The most destructive landslides have been 36). by\r\nearthquakes that started the material moving. However, excessive\r\nrainfall on steep angles. Rapid temperature 37).\r\ncan also\r\ncause land to slide by expanding soil formations. Forest fires are\r\nindirectly responsible for landslides because they take away slope\r\nvegetation, making 38.)\r\neasier. Man can also cause slides\r\nby mining the Earth and overdeveloping hillsides.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>gak bisa b inggris..... </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>artinya nyawa taruhan</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-in-the-gaps-from-thes-words-energeticshy-funnyand-selfis-557",
            "question": "Fill in the gaps from thes words : energetic,shy funny,and selfish\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>isi celah dari kata-kata ini : energik , malu lucu , dan egois</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. funny</p><p>2. shy</p><p>3. energetic</p><p>4. selfish</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>1. Fill in the gaps. Use the words in the box !</p><p>a. My uncle loves to tell jokes to make us laugh. He is . . . . . . . .</p><p>b. She never talks to a stranger. She is very . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>c. I like doing sports and physical activities. I\u2019m very . . . . . . . . . . . . . .</p><p>d. Don\u2019t just think of yourself, that\u2019s so . . . . . . . .</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-month-is-april-an-june-isi-titik2-n-351",
            "question": "The............ month is............. april an june. isi titik2 nya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>the May month is between april and june</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-in-they-read-a-book-under-a-tree-yes-a-they-are-h-they-wers-581",
            "question": "6 in they read a book under a tree?    Yes\r\na. They are\r\nh. They wers\r\nc. They will\r\nd. They do\r\n7. We can buy ruler in the\r\na. Stationery store\r\nb. Candy store\r\ne. Electronic store\r\nd. Music store\r\n8. Rama: Look at these shoes, Lita,\r\nThey are very nice\r\nLita : Yes?\r\nRama ninety nine thousand rupiah\r\na Of course\r\nb. Sure\r\nc. Don't worry\r\nd. How much are they\r\nThe conversation below for question number 9-11\r\nRoger . Hey, Rudi ! Let's play basketball today, shall we?\r\nRudi : Oh no, not today. Sorry. Maybe tomorrow.\r\nRoger \u00b7 What's the matter?\r\nRudi I'm not feeling very well. I've got a beadache.\r\nRoger; Oh sorry to hear that. Here. Take this. You should take an spirin\r\nRudi\r\n\u2022 Er. Ok.\r\n9. What does Roger want to do ?\r\na. Play basketball\r\nb. Reads book\r\nc. Camping\r\nd. Playing football\r\n10. What does Roger give to Rudi?\r\na. A baskztball\r\nb. An aspirin\r\nC. A sboes\r\nd. A medicine\r\n11. Who take the aspirio ?\r\na Roger\r\nb. Rudi\r\nc. Sinta\r\nd. Budi\r\n12. The students go to school...... (setiap hari)\r\na. Every day\r\nb. Every Sunday\r\nc. Tomorrow\r\nd. Yesterday\r\n13. My living room is not.......(besar), but I am happy.\r\na. Small\r\n6. Big\r\nc. Beautiful\r\nd. Cheap\r\n\r\ntolong di bantu jawabanya\r\ntrimakasih\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>6. a. they are</p><p>7. stationery store</p><p>8. d. how much are they?</p><p>9. a. play basketball</p><p>10. b. an aspirin</p><p>11. b. Rudi</p><p>12. a. every day</p><p>13. b. big</p><p></p><p>semoga terbantu ya\u270c</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "exercise-five-give-questions-1-where-the-two-women-lived-323",
            "question": "EXERCISE FIVE    Give questions :-\r\n?\r\n1. Where\r\n?\r\nThe two women lived in the same house.\r\n2. How many\r\nThey each had a child.\r\n?\r\n3. What happened\r\nIt happened that one of the children died one night.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Where did the two women live?</p><p>2. How many child they have each?</p><p>3. What happened one night?</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><strong>1. Kalimat dalam </strong><em><strong>past tense</strong></em><strong>, jadi pertanyaan menggunakan kata kerja </strong><em><strong>did </strong></em><strong>setelah kata tanya.</strong></p><p><strong>2. Menanyakan jumlah. Yang menjadi obyek dengan jumlah ditanyakan adalah &#039;a child&#039;. Subyeknya adalah </strong><em><strong>they </strong></em><strong>yang merupakan</strong><em><strong> </strong></em><strong>kata ganti jamak, jadi kata kerja di pertanyaan menggunakan </strong><em><strong>have</strong></em><strong>.</strong></p><p><strong>3. Yang ditanyakan adalah apa, jadi peristiwa yang menjadi jawaban tidak disebutkan di pertanyaan.</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "besi-tanah-udara-merupakan-contoh-962",
            "question": "Besi tanah udara merupakan contoh\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>benda yang dapat di perbarui</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf jika salah:)</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "do-you-think-its-important-to-educate-people-about-endanger-spec-462",
            "question": "Do you think it's important to educate people about endanger species?    a.\r\n\r\nNot, it isn't.\r\n\r\nb.\r\n\r\nNo important.\r\n\r\nc.\r\n\r\nYes, it is.\r\n\r\nd.\r\n\r\nYes, there are not.\r\n\r\n\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>The answer is C. Yes, it is</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>c.</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>yes,it is</p><p>ratinya ya itu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "14-today-toothache-15labdi-the-library-b-pe-read-16-safina-li-276",
            "question": "14. Today    toothache\r\n15.Labdi the library\r\nb. Pe\r\nRead\r\n16. Safina liver\r\nBrooch\r\nd. User\r\n17. Below are doors found in stationery SCE, CHOTE\r\na. Peagi\r\ne Shagede\r\n13. Wem shop for starts, trous and socks in the\r\na Bookstore\r\nb. Clothing Store\r\nc. Eladrone store\r\n&amp; Toys\r\n19. The meaning of coucha\r\n2. Batuk\r\nb. Salute\r\ne. Flu\r\nd. Sakit kepala\r\n20. The lang\r\na la\r\nb. On\r\nthe window and the bod (di antara).\r\nc. Between\r\nd. Opposite\r\n\r\ntolong d bantu jawabanya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>13. B. clothing store</p><p>19. a. batuk</p><p>20. c. between</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>nomor lainnya sy g paham maksud pertanyaan</p><p>maaf</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}